obsidiandawn.com 2012-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Obsidian Dawn

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.obsidiandawn.com/contact).

At ObsidianDawn.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.obsidiandawn.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.obsidiandawn.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Collected Information**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name or email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**Information Use**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to respond better to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you))
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
  * To send periodic emails  
If you have signed up for our newsletter, you will receive updates whenever a new resource is added to ObsidianDawn.com. 

Note: You may opt out of this newsletter at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature

**Protection**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

Any information given while purchasing one of our licenses is collected by PayPal. We do not gather or have access to any of your financial information that your provide to PayPal for your purchase. The information that we are given (name, email, etc), we gather only long enough to display it to you upon your receipt.

**Cookies**

ObsidianDawn.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, and customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

**Privacy**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.obsidiandawn.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.obsidiandawn.com and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

  * Google Adsense
  * BuySellAds.com

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.obsidiandawn.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

ObsidianDawn.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes**

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page.

This policy was last modified on 06/24/2011.
